Cover Letter

SUBJECT: Job Application

Dear,

Job Fair Recruiting Agent

STI Academic Center, University Parkway Drive, Taguig 1630

Metro Manila

With Regards,

Hereby I send an application letter and resume in response to Job Fair event happening these consecutive days at STI College City.

I have bad and not fully experience at the field of Information Technology. I realize that my resume that I submitted cannot explain my qualifications in depth. Therefore, I really hope that there is chance interview, which I can explain how the potential in me and my ministry will give tremendous asset and potential for your company.

Sincerely,

Gacilo, Ariel Jericko F.

Table of Contents

Page 1 – Cover letter

Page 2 – Table of Contents

Page 3 - 6 – Resume

Page 7-8 Licenses, Awards or Certificates

Page 9 Goals and Plans for the future

Page 9 – Work Samples

ARIEL JERICKO F. GACILO

Email: <u>bokzgacilo@gmail.com</u>

Contact: 0976-222-0951

Address: Bldg. 32, Cabrera St. Paclasan, Roxas,

Oriental Mindoro



OBJECTIVE

To know more about my chosen career and to be able to develop my skills when it comes to my field, to work in a reputable firm that could enhance my skills and lastly, to help the company to the best of my abilities.

SKILLS SUMMARY

- With knowledge in Microsoft, Google and WPS Offices
- Can work in cross platform computer environment
- Diagnose and troubleshoot computer hardware and software failures
- Knowledge in mobile app and web development
- Knowledge on how to implement minimalist web design
- Installing and configuring computer networks
- Diagnose and troubleshoot computer internet and network failures
- Knowledge in multimedia audio and visual environment editing
- Knowledge in photo editing software (Photoshop, Illustrator and Lightroom)

TOOLS. APPLICATIONS and ENVIRONMENT

- Microsoft, Google and WPS Office
- Adobe Product (Photoshop, Illustrator and Lightroom)
- Android Studio
- Xampp
- PHPmyadmin
- Node IS
- Cisco Packet Tracer
- Postman
- NPM and YARN

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE, TECHNOLOGY and FRAMEWORKS

- HTML
- CSS
 - o Bootstrap
 - o Materiallize CSS
 - o Bulma
- PHP
- Java
- C#
- MongoDB
- SQL
 - o MySQL
 - o SQLite
- Javascript
 - o React JS
 - o Angular JS
 - o Ionic
 - o Node JS
 - o Vanilla

WORKING EXPERIENCES

Guidance Office Assistant STI College Global City

Dec 2018 – Feb 2019 STI Academic Center, University Parkway Drive,

Taguig

Registrar Assistant STI College Global City

Nov 2018 – Dec 2018 STI Academic Center, University Parkway Drive,

Taguig

EDUCATION

Tertiary: STI College Global City (2019 - Present)

STI Academic Center, University Parkway Drive, Taguig

COURSE: Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Senior High School: STI College Global City (2017 - 2019)

STI Academic Center, University Parkway Drive, Taguig

TRACK: Information Technology in Mobile App and Web

Development

Junior High School: Fe del Mundo National High School (2013-2017)

Mansalay, Oriental Mindoro

Elementary: Roxas Central School (2007-2013)

Paclasan, Roxas, Oriental Mindoro

CERTIFICATION AND TRAINING

Certification of Completion in SAP Business ONE

March 2021

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Nick Name : Bok

Gender : 21 years of age
Date of Birth : October 04, 2000

Place of Birth : Roxas, Oriental Mindoro

Civil Status : Single
Citizenship : Filipino
Height : 5'6"
Weight : 52 kgs.

Religion : Roman Catholic
Dialects : Filipino and English

Mother's Maiden Name : Blessie Falogme Fernando

Occupation : Teacher

Father's Name : Arellano Mansalay Gacilo

Occupation : Family Business Manager and House Keeper

CHARACTER REFERENCES

Mark Frederick Salonga STI College Global City

Maria Antonia Mariano STI College Global City

I declare under oath that this Personal Data Sheet has been accomplished by me, and is a true correct the falsification on willful omission herein shall be sufficient reason for dismissal or refused of employment by the company/institution.

I also authorize the institution head/ authorize representative to verify/validate the contents stated herein. I trust that this information shall remain confidential.

Ariel Jerickoff. Gacilo

(Applicant)

Licenses / Awards / Certificate

Certificate of Completion





STI College
STI Academic Center, University Parkway Drive, Taguig, Metro Manila

Certificate of Completion

This certificate is issued to

ARIEL JERICKO GACILO

for having successfully completed the training course in

SAP Business One

SAP Advance (Implementation & Support)

given this June 06,2022 at FIT Academy, Makati City



Certificate Number:FIT-0120220610144631



Ms. Marilyn D. Bones Training and Education Director

Licenses / Awards / Certificate

Certificate of Completion





STI College STI Academic Center, University Parkway Drive, Taguig, Metro Manila



Certificate of Completion

This certificate is issued to

Ariel Jericko Gacilo

for having successfully completed the training course in

SAP Business One

SAP Basic (Financials and Logistics)

given this March 2021 at STI College - Global City



Certificate Number:FIT-012021033054114



Ms. Marilyn D. Bones Training and Education Director

Goals and Plans for the future

Goals:

- 1. To be successful and financially stable
- 2. To make my parents, siblings and my lover proud
- 3. To have a continuous flow of income
- 4. To have a good and winning investment
- 5. To be a role model to new generation

Plans:

- 1. After 10-12 years of working, I will retire and start a business.
- 2. Once I get my first million I will start my business venture
- 3. To settle with my lover and my business

Work Samples

For my work samples you can visit the link below:

https://bokzgacilo.github.io/portfolio/